[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Deserts are advancing and taking over the land. For instance, in Mali the desert is advancing at this speed.", "correct_answer": "11 miles per year", "incorrect_answers": ["37 miles per year", "4 miles per year", "23 miles per year"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of cheese is one of the ingredients of the Insalata Caprese salad?", "correct_answer": "Buffalo mozzarella", "incorrect_answers": ["Brie", "Cheddar cheese", "Ricotta cheese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the Apollo 8 space trip, the astronauts used silly putty to fasten objects.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Harvard dropouts first acting role was in Mystic Pizza, in 1988.  He lived next door to historian, Howard Zinn.", "correct_answer": "Matt Damon", "incorrect_answers": ["Mark Ruffalo", "Ed Norton", "Ed Burns"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Victoria is the capital of the Republic of Seychelles.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these fish is least likely to be found in seawater?", "correct_answer": "Tench", "incorrect_answers": ["Tuna", "Tarpon", "Trumpetfish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fictional character Jack Ryan is flown to what U.S. aircraft carrier to explain the details of what is happening with the Red October?", "correct_answer": "U.S.S. Enterprise", "incorrect_answers": ["U.S.S. Kitty Hawk", "U.S.S. Nimitz", "U.S.S. Abraham Lincoln"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country had the largest prison population for 2006?", "correct_answer": "Peoples Republic of China", "incorrect_answers": ["The United States", "Turkey", "Nigeria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the length of the 2007 film adaptation of the graphic novel 300?", "correct_answer": "117 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["111 minutes", "125 minutes", "100 minutes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "With Night of the Living Dead and Dawn of the Dead being the previous two, what is the name of the third instalment in George A. Romeros zombie saga?", "correct_answer": "Day of the Dead", "incorrect_answers": ["Morning of the Dead", "Afternoon of the Dead", "Noon of the Dead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This mineral, an important component of all living creatures cellular membranes, is one of the major minerals required in the structural composition of bones and teeth.", "correct_answer": "Phosphorus", "incorrect_answers": ["Iron", "Potassium", "Fluoride"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Laws of physics are properties, common to all material systems.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]